Checking landing area.
Have everyone disembark! Hurry!
We're saved.
We'll be safe here.
Everyone's off the ship.
We're heading back to the battlefield.
Leon's Dad.
We'll go with you.
You're hurt. Students
should stay evacuated.
B-But...
It's all right, boys.
You've already proven your courage.
Ladies...
Leon will be fine.
Trust him.
Trust him?
Trust Leon?
Wait, wait, wait.
There's no way.
A-At this rate, we'll be wiped out!
Merging with that odd vehicle
didn't do much to help you!
Villains of the kingdom,
I'll kill you all!
He's lost his mind.
The magical item has completely
taken over his body.
Damn it.
Are you that desperate to
keep fighting, old man?!
Trapped in
a Dating Sim
Trapped in a Dating Sim
Trapped in a Dating Sim 2
There's a way to stop that monster.
I Don't Care About That!
Really, Marie? I mean, Lady Marie?
Yeah.
I only watched that cutscene from
my brother's save file, but...
That monster is being summoned
by an item called a magic flute.
She's right. I witnessed monsters
being summoned on our school trip.
A magic flute?
That ship is the source
of the flute's sound.
Let's go. We have to end this suffering.
Okay. Head to the owner
of the magic flute!
What? Who do you think you are?
Don't tell us what to do.
You haven't figured it out yet?!
Kyle, just do it.
Honestly, you never change, mistress.
What's wrong? Is that all you've got?
Shut up, fallen warrior!
Watch out!
Damn it!
I can't, I can't, I can't!
What an unladylike voice.
It's all right, though.
Eare?
Is that what you're calling
me? How congenial.
In any case, there's
nothing to worry about.
That sourpuss will escort us.
Energy fully charged.
Firing boson particle cannon.
Wh-What was that light?
I've never seen such magic before.
Yes, it's magic.
Incredibly powerful magic.
N-No, that's...
The demon lord's wrath!
Now, before that monster regenerates!
Yes, I know.
We'll be their backup!
Don't tell us what to do!
There it is! The magic flute!
That's...
Hertrude!
How did you get here?
No, wait. Did you play the flute?
I'll destroy them all.
Please stop. At this rate,
everyone will die.
So?
So the people of the
principality will die, too!
Let's put an end to this!
No.
Never.
You...
If you want to kill me, then kill me!
That won't stop the guardian of the land!
It'll keep reviving!
I understand that you hate us, but
what's the point in continuing to fight?
Won't it just cause more pointless deaths?
Oh, shut up.
The principality can trace its
roots back to the Holfort royals.
The principality? I don't care
what happens to it anymore.
What?
What did you say?
I don't care
what happens to the principality
that exploited me and my sister.
We didn't know they killed our
parents, and we let them use us.
Everything I loved has been taken
from me, even my sister Rauda!
I don't trust anyone anymore.
They should all just go away!
I want nothing more than to
destroy this hopeless world!
I want to avenge my sister and parents!
Isn't that right? Why?
Why couldn't we be happy? Why?!
S-Still, this is wrong.
What good is revenge?
That's not what your sister wants!
Shut up!
Shut your mouth, dreamer!
Ms. Marie?
Wh-What are you saying?
Whose side are you on?
I don't know, and I don't care!
That's just a bunch of
idealistic nonsense!
Revenge is wrong? Whatever!
Who do you think you are?
Her sister wouldn't want that?
You've got some nerve
speaking on her behalf!
B-But...
So she's supposed to accept her
misery and not seek revenge?
Does she not have the right to be happy?
What about her feelings?!
You have no problem lecturing her,
but if you lost your loved ones,
would you take it lying down?
You wouldn't avenge them
even if it's wrong?
I-I...
Have you ever experienced
unbearable regret?
Has anyone you loved ever died?
You never get to see them again!
It hurts when people you
love die. It really hurts!
W-Wait. Right now, stopping
that monster is our priority.
Shut up!
If this is all it takes to destroy
this world, then I say let it happen!
I know it's wrong and that we
shouldn't let it happen, but...
but we still can't stop it!
I never thought the Saint who only
cares about money would defend me.
I'm not defending you.
I just can't stand those two and
their main character syndrome.
I never would have felt
like this if not for you.
Are you really okay with this, though?
No.
Not at all.
But...
Hurry. Get away from me.
What's wrong?
The cost of summoning guardians
with this flute is the user's life.
Now that I've broken the contract,
I'll never be able to play it again,
and the guardian will try to kill me.
What?
B-But...
And the principality will surrender.
Get away, everyone!
Livia, are you all right?
Vandel!
What's going on?
What are they doing here?
Ms. Hertrude's here, too?
Vandel, enough!
Fanoss has declared the fighting over!
Princess, do not worry.
I'll kill that villain this instant.
I shall obliterate the kingdom's forces.
No! It's over, Vandel!
Princess...
Father, Mother...
Are you sure this was the right choice?
Both the people and nobility
wish to fight the kingdom,
which is why the king and
queen had to go away.
There's no point in crying over it now.
You'll get to avenge your family.
If you're a knight of the principality,
forget your meaningless regrets.
Princess.
Vandel...
Do not worry. I shall fight for you and
your sister in your parents' place.
Vandel...
I swear on this sword...
This cannot end.
This cannot be the end!
Vandel...
I will keep fighting after my death.
That is all I can do to atone.
That is my...
code of chivalry!
You bastard!
Damn it!
Luxion!
Damn you!
Sorry, old man.
Impact.
Vandel!
Vandel! Vandel! Vandel!
P-Princess...
This is the end for me.
Please don't leave me.
Princess...
Hey, you!
Don't die yet!
What are you saying?
He's the Black Knight!
I know that! How many times do
you think he's beaten me? Still...
Are you going to leave her all alone?
There are those in the kingdom
who care for the princess.
Now I can finally...
I lost.
Princess, please...
Vandel...
Be happy.
Vandel!
Don't waste any time.
If you don't get out of here
quickly, you'll be killed, too.
But...
Come on, you two.
Hurry, please.
End this.
Leon Fou Bartfort...
Now, what should I do?
Not much can be done against an
endlessly regenerating enemy.
Olivia is severely weakened.
Luxion.
What is it?
Understood.
The main ship is out of range,
so I'll gather energy in the Arroganz.
Out of range? For what?
Olivia's power.
Mr. Leon...
Livia... Angie...
I'll add Olivia's wavelength
to your attack.
It's time to go big or go home.
Don't let them get close!
Don't tell us what to do!
Fabulous.
He saved me?
He defeated it!
Yes!
We finally defeated the final boss.
Arroganz has reached its limit, though.
Leon!
Oh, my.
Hey, did I do the right thing?
I said I wanted to live a
peaceful life as an NPC,
but tons of people ended up dying.
I killed a ton of people, too.
If I were the protagonist of a story,
I could've done a better job.
You're overestimating your own importance.
The war would've happened either way,
and nobody expected much from you.
You're a real dick.
So I am just an NPC.
Anyway, I'm surprised we won.
Isn't that because this is the world
of your so-called "otome game"?
Huh? What do you mean?
You're always complaining about
it while hurling obscenities.
How "love will save the world."
Leon!
Mr. Leon!
Angie, Livia.
You may be an NPC, but their love is real.
The truth is that love ended the fighting.
Isn't it about time you
made your decision?
You love them, don't you?
You don't get it.
I want to take good care of
them because I love them.
I hadn't thought about what
I'd say, but for now...
I'm back.
The fighting's over, peace has been
restored, and my brother's engaged?
Master.
Leon's screams echo across
an inescapable future!
Master?
The final episode,
"This World Is Tough for Mobs."
The final boss of life is romantic events!